A Guide to The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records, 1981-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
The Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia Committee Records 1981-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/3.891
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1989 July 10.
Contents List
- Audit Committee (2 folders) 1983-1986 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1986-1987 Mar (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1984 May (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1984 Oct (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting (2 folders) 1985 Jan (Box 1)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1985 Mar (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1985 May (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1985 Oct (Box 2)
- Committee Agenda (2 folders) 1981-1987 (Box 2)
- Educational Policy Committee (correspondence) 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- Executive Committee 1985 (Box 2)
- Executive Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1981-1985 (Box 2)
- Executive Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1985-1986 Nov (Box 3)
- Finance Committee (2 folders) 1985-1986 Apr (Box 3)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 3)
- Health Affairs Committee Correspondence 1985-1987 (Box 3)